const verses = [
    {
      question: "Psalm 51:10",
      answer: "Create in me a clean heart, O God, and renew a right spirit within me."
    },
    {
      question: "Philippians 4:13",
      answer: "I can do all things through Christ who strengthens me."
    },
    {
      question: "John 3:16",
      answer: "For God so loved the world that He gave His only begotten Son, that whoever believes in Him should not perish but have everlasting life."
    },
    {
      question: "Romans 8:28",
      answer: "And we know that in all things God works for the good of those who love Him, who have been called according to His purpose."
    },
    {
      question: "Proverbs 3:5-6",
      answer: "Trust in the LORD with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding; in all your ways submit to Him, and He will make your paths straight."
    },
    {
      question: "Isaiah 41:10",
      answer: "Fear not, for I am with you; be not dismayed, for I am your God. I will strengthen you, I will help you, I will uphold you with My righteous right hand."
    },
    {
      question: "2 Timothy 1:7",
      answer: "For God has not given us a spirit of fear, but of power and of love and of a sound mind."
    },
    {
      question: "Matthew 11:28",
      answer: "Come to Me, all you who are weary and burdened, and I will give you rest."
    },
    {
      question: "Joshua 1:9",
      answer: "Have I not commanded you? Be strong and courageous. Do not be afraid; do not be discouraged, for the LORD your God will be with you wherever you go."
    },
    {
      question: "Ephesians 2:8-9",
      answer: "For by grace you have been saved through faith, and that not of yourselves; it is the gift of God, not of works, lest anyone should boast."
    }
  ];
  
  export default verses;